Laundry, Dry Cleaning and Dye House Workers' International Union Files 6293
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Laundry, Dry Cleaning and Dye House Workers' International Union Files
1971- 2002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Laundry, Dry Cleaning and Dye House Workers' International Union
6293
2.5 cubic feet
2.5 linear ft.
Records.
6756611
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 27, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 26, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Laundry workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Textile workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Laundry, Dry Cleaning, and Dye House Workers' International Union; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Laundry, Dry Cleaning, and Dye House Workers' International Union; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees. Local 75; UNITE HERE (Organization)
6756611
- Executive Board and regional meeting minutes; Subject files A-M. (Box 1)
  - Executive Board Meeting, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Antioch Meetings (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Concord Martinez Meetings, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Monterey Meetings, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Excuses, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - S.F. Policy Committee, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - San Francisco Regular Meeting - minutes, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Santa Cruz (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Grievance, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Citation, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - American Linen Service Invoice 3/92, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bell's Office Machines, 1974-1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - By Laws of Textile Processors Local 75 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - By-Law Revision Local 75 (6-2-76), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Beeson, Tayer, Lilbert, & Livingston, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Black Mountain Spring Water 9/1990 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Old Calendars 1981 1;2;3;4;5 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Candidate for office - forms 1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Communications, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Air Conditioner, 1967-1999 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Burglary - Jan 20, 1986 - 2nd Floor Local 75 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - DY-Dee Wash, 1966-1973 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Elevator 1981 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Form 5500 Pension 1980 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Fax Machine 1/1996 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Fire master Service, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Fire 1/13/1994 damage back bldg. 355 Hayes St. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Garage Door, 1986-1998 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Gilroy, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Keys, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Janitorial Service, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Labor Law Bulletin, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Microfilm Information 1996 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Mita DC 1255 copy machine 7/13/95, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Merger San Jose w/ San Francisco, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous.. Unfair Labor Practice, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Subject files N-Z. (Box 2)
  - National Labor Relation, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - OSHA, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - De Jager & Reilly Plumbing 260 Linden SF, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Pitney Bowes Contracts, 1980-1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Panasonic Copy Machine 9/1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Panasonic Copier 3030 9-1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Post Office, 1986-1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Pen. TR. Teamster Pension Office, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Pen TR. Teamster Welfare Office, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Perm DisabilityGDL's, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Pacific Bell, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - PGE, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Rental - 355 Hayes Street, S.F. 1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Roof, 1997-2001 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 1992 Rental 355 Hayes S. S.F. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - See's Candies, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Concrete Sidewalk Repair, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Sunset Scavenger & Recycling (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - San Francisco Unified School District, 1986-1991 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - San Francisco Meeting Hall, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Sacramento Meeting Schedules (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Shop Stewards - San Francisco, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Shop Stewards - San Jose, 1975-1980 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - New Employer - Memo of Agreement (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Marin County - Stipulations (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Jose Solorzano, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Telephone Service Repair, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - 3M, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Telephone Lists - San Francisco, 1986-1998 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Telephone List of Employee's, 1987-1994 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - San Jose Area, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Teamsters' Local 856 - Agreements, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Water, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - S.F. Water Dept., 1991 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Water Heater, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - W-4 Forms, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Workmen's Compensation - Welfare, 1961-1978 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Agreements; Negotiations; Out-of-Business files; Welfare files, 1990-1996; Welfare program booklets; Union shop display cards; Meeting minutes. (Box 3)
  - American Linen S.S.F. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - S.F. Neg. American Linen S.F., 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Exchange S.F. (office), 1995-1998 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Marin County Neg., 1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Moderne Drapery Service, 1993-1997 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - United People (negotiation), 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Cathedral Hill, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Sheraton Palace Hotel, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Health & Welfare Minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Health & Welfare Communications, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Health & Welfare Bank Statements, 1995-1997 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - H & W (Medical Fund), 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Health & Welfare Financial Report, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - H & W (checks issued), 1991 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Health & Welfare (Drug Program), 1993 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - S.D. Sicotte - Hemming Morse (H & W), 1992-1996 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Zenith Administrators (H & W), 1992 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Cobra, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Rael & Letson (H & W), 1997 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - S.F. Health & Welfare Trust, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - San Jose Regular Meeting, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - 8-30-71, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 22)